Pavlo Dovbysh

Mobile App Developer

I am Pavlo Dovbysh, a dedicated app developer with 5 years of experience in crafting outstanding digital solutions. My journey in app development is driven by a commitment to continuous learning and growth. I'm a hard worker who enjoys challenges that seek to push my learning experience and knowledge.

pavlo.dovbysh.dev@gmail.com

+48 (57)-358-1531

Gdansk, Poland

in linkedin.com/in/pavlo-dovbysh

WORK EXPERIENCE

iOS/Android Developer

Dirk Rossman GmbH

08/2023 - 04/2024

Shopping App

- o Refactored and updated the app's UI (Product Gallery | Detailed Product Description | Shopping Cart | Order Summary | Checking and Shipping Status) using React Native, enhancing user experience.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to improve app performance using XCTest, Espresso, and JUnit.
- Tested against a user base of 10M+ with 20K+ active daily users.

AppStore Google Play Store

React Native Developer

Yescapa SAS

02/2023 - 08/2024

P2P RV Rental App

- o Implemented a nearby feature using the Mapbox API to enhance user interaction.
- Worked on chat features through an integration with the Salesforce Chat SDK and MessageKit.
- o Enhanced app security for payment and user information management by applying OWASP best practices.

Google Play Store App Store

Mobile Developer

Exposit Consulting Sp

02/2020 - 11/2022

Achieved

- o Maintained and updated a real estate mobile application (iOS/Android) for client Morizon LTD.
- Developed a simple Diet mobile application using React
- Launched an educational app (Librus) aimed at improving student-parent communication.

App Store Google Play Store

Intern Yandex for Apps

05/2019 - 12/2019

EDUCATION

Applied Information Technology Vinnytsia National Technical University

Ехро **Android Swift**

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript Java Kotlin

UI Animation

TypeScript

Node.js

AndroidSDK

React Native

iOS SDK Detox

Espresso

OWASP

Appium **XCTest**

Charles Proxy

Context AP

Firebase

SQLite

MySQL

Redux

MongoDB

MobX

PostgreSQL

GraphQL

Realm

Scrum

AWS

Azure **Agile Software Development**

Supabase BaaS

UI/UX

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Retail eCommerce

Real Estate

SaaS

Healthcare | Hospitality

Education

Finance

Entertainment

Travel & Tourism

Fitness | Gymnation | Diet | Yoga